question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In the Greek Mythology, the god of war is called Mars.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "A wyvern is the same as a dragon.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "Ska&eth;i is the Norse Goddess of skiing, mountains, winter and bowhunting.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In the Greek Mythology, the Gorgon can turn those who behold her to stone.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In Greek mythology, Hera is the goddess of harvest.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]

"""
question_data = [
{"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
         "you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
         "answer": "False"},
{"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]

"""
